Eli Pandolfo

Software Developer

Personal Info

Email

elipandolfo@gmail.com

Phone

• (802) 498-8164

Github

• github.com/elip12

Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/eli-pandolfo
Website

elip12.github.io

Professional Skills

Development Practices

- · CI/CD
- Agile
- TDD/BDD
- RESTful API Architecture
- · Relational Database Design
- Software Testing

Languages

- Go
- Python
- Bash
- JavaScript & HTML
- · SQL
- C & C++
- Java

Tools

- UNIX/Linux
- Kubernetes
- Saltstack
- AWS
- Terraform
- Postgres
- Django
- Vue

Certifications

· AWS Technical Professional

About Me

Software engineer at Robinhood recently graduated from UC Santa Cruz with advanced programming experience and coursework in math and biology. Intent on bridging the gap between development, especially around open-source orchestration tools, and operations, including debugging, linux systems, and networking. In my down time I bike, surf, play jazz sax, and am an avid backpacker and skier. Ready to learn and contribute in any way possible.

Experience

Infrastructure Engineer Robinhood, Menlo Park, CA 2020 - present

- Implemented autoscaling policies saving the company 50K/month in infrastructure costs
- Strengthen infrastructure quality & reliability, promote anti-fragility, and enhance developer productivity by extending Kubernetes APIs and reducing dependency on Terraform & Salt.
- Lessen frequency and impact of sevs by identifying and eliminating P0 risks, with the goal of carrying Robinhood's systems to 99.999% reliability.

Lab Programmer LEEPS Lab, UC Santa Cruz, CA 2017 - 2018, 2019 - 2020

- Developed real-time multiplayer economics experiments for research into markets, game theory, and decision-making.
- · Wrote Python and Bash scripts to analyze and visualize experiment data.
- · Set up and maintained a public Linux production server.
- · Hired, trained, and supervised four lab programmers.

Software Engineering Intern productOps, Santa Cruz, CA 2018 - 2019

- Developed Node API and Postgres database that simplifies and streamlines the creation of AWS infrastructure, reducing startup overhead for new projects.
- Wrote end-to-end and integration tests for Angular/Node web apps, ensuring safe updates to production applications with 1000+ users.

Education

BS Computer Science UC Santa Cruz 2016 - 2020

- · GPA: 3.96
- Regent's Scholarship
- · College Scholars Program
- Undergraduate bioinformatics & machine learning research with <u>Lings</u> Lab
- Areas of focus: bioinformatics, computational economics, data wrangling & machine learning, parallel processing

42 Piscine 42 Silicon Valley 2017

Four-week intensive C coding program at School 42 in Fremont, CA

Projects

Genome Wide Association Study Lings Lab, UC Santa Cruz

- Microbial GWAS program that uses statistical relational learning to predict genetic causes of bacterial phenotypes.
- Successfully identified genes in *E. coli* known to cause antibiotic resistance, outperforming a state-of-the-art method.

Computational Economics Experiment LEEPS Lab, UC Santa Cruz

- Multiplayer web app with Vue.js UI simulating people waiting in a queue.
- Players trade places with each other for money in real time.

StenoScribe Android App Mobile Apps Class, UC Santa Cruz

 Mobile app for streamlining note-taking during meetings. Users can instantly share speech-to-text transcriptions, photos, and documents.